<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                   xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
                   xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
                                       http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-latest.xsd">

    <changeSet id="002" author="vitikova" dbms="postgresql">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO "public"."comment" ("id", "news_id", "time", "text", "username")
            VALUES (1, 1, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Wow, this is truly extraordinary! Im blown away by the creativity and talent showcased here.',
                    'username123'),
                   (2, 2, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'I cant believe how much effort and dedication must have gone into creating something this beautiful. Absolutely stunning!',
                    'coolcat85'),
                   (3, 7, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'These findings are groundbreaking and have the potential to change the way we think about the world. Impressive work!',
                    'fearlessrunner'),
                   (4, 7, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Im so inspired by this. Its a great reminder that with hard work and determination, anything is possible!',
                    'fearlessrunner'),
                   (5, 7, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'This is an important topic that needs to be discussed more. Thank you for shedding light on it.',
                    'musiclover27'),
                   (6, 3, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'I never cease to be amazed by the level of innovation in this field. Truly mind-boggling!',
                    'adventureseeker'),
                   (7, 4, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Youve captured the essence of the subject matter perfectly. It evokes so many emotions and thoughts.',
                    'techguru99'),
                   (8, 5, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Bravo! This is exactly what we need right now. Your message is powerful and impactful.',
                    'techguru99'),
                   (9, 10, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Im in awe of the level of detail and craftsmanship displayed here. Pure artistry at its finest!',
                    'adventureseeker'),
                   (10, 10, '2024-02-17 19:06:01.405015',
                    'Thank you for sharing this information. Its eye-opening and thought-provoking. Keep up the great work!',
                    'smarthacker76');

            INSERT INTO "public"."news" ("id", "time", "text", "title", "user_id")
            VALUES (1, '2024-02-17 16:31:38.166727',
                    'Researchers have recently identified a previously unknown species of marine organisms during a deep-sea expedition in the Atlantic Ocean.',
                    'Scientists Discover New Species of Marine Life in the Atlantic Ocean', 1),
                   (2, '2024-02-17 16:31:39.772884',
                    'Economists predict a decline in the pace of global economic expansion in the upcoming quarter due to various factors, including trade tensions and geopolitical uncertainties.',
                    'Global Economic Growth Expected to Slow Down in the Next Quarter', 2),
                   (3, '2024-02-17 16:31:40.477176',
                    'A recent scientific study suggests a strong correlation between quality sleep patterns and enhanced productivity levels, highlighting the importance of adequate rest for optimal performance.',
                    'New Study Reveals Link Between Sleep and Productivity', 3),
                   (4, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Heads of state and global leaders convene in Paris to discuss urgent measures and collaborate on combating climate change and implementing sustainable practices worldwide.',
                    'World Leaders Gather for Climate Change Summit in Paris', 4),
                   (5, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Scientists have achieved a significant breakthrough in cancer research, potentially opening doors to innovative treatment methods that could revolutionize cancer care.',
                    'Breakthrough in Cancer Research Could Lead to New Treatment Options', 5),
                   (6, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'A prominent technology company introduces a cutting-edge smartphone model equipped with groundbreaking features designed to enhance user experience and redefine the industry standard.',
                    'Tech Giant Unveils Next Generation Smartphone with Revolutionary Features', 7),
                   (7, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Against all odds, a determined sports team stages an extraordinary comeback to win a crucial championship game, creating history in the world of sports.',
                    'Sports Team Makes Historic Comeback in Championship Game', 6),
                   (8, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'A celebrated artists latest exhibition garners overwhelming praise and accolades from art critics and enthusiasts alike, solidifying their position as a leading figure in the art world.',
                    'Renowned Artists Exhibition Receives Rave Reviews from Critics', 6),
                   (9, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Researchers announce a promising breakthrough in vaccine development, potentially offering a new solution for combating a life-threatening disease that has plagued communities for years.',
                    'Scientists Develop Promising Vaccine for Deadly Disease', 8),
                   (10, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'A significant cybersecurity breach leads to the exposure of sensitive user information, raising concerns about data privacy and the need for enhanced online security measures.',
                    'Major Cybersecurity Breach Exposes Millions of User Data', 9),
                   (11, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'The tense situation in a troubled region reaches a boiling point as political unrest escalates.',
                    'Political Unrest Escalates in Troubled Region', 9),
                   (12, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Unprecedented heatwave conditions scorch several countries, setting new temperature records.',
                    'Record-breaking Heatwave Sweeps Across Several Countries', 8),
                   (13, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'A recent study highlights the correlation between excessive social media use and mental health issues.',
                    'New Study Shows Link Between Social Media Use and Mental Health Issues', 7),
                   (14, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Exciting plans are underway as a tech company reveals intentions to launch a program for lunar tourism.',
                    'Tech Company Announces Plans to Launch Lunar Tourism Program', 6),
                   (15, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Residential areas face imminent danger as a raging wildfire threatens homes, prompting necessary evacuations.',
                    'Wildfire Threatens Residential Areas, Evacuations Ordered', 5),
                   (16, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'In a surprising twist, a celebrity couple announces their secret wedding, stunning fans and the media.',
                    'Celebrity Couple Announces Surprise Wedding', 4),
                   (17, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Scientists find compelling evidence linking air pollution to an increased risk of respiratory diseases.',
                    'Study Finds Link Between Air Pollution and Respiratory Diseases', 3),
                   (18, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'The renowned music festival returns, attracting global attention with its star-studded lineup of performers.',
                    'World-renowned Music Festival Returns with Star-studded Lineup', 3),
                   (19, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'Controversial legislation sparks widespread protests and ignites a wave of public outcry.',
                    'Controversial Legislation Sparks Protests and Public Outcry', 2),
                   (20, '2024-02-17 16:31:41.232163',
                    'New research offers promising breakthroughs and potential treatments for Alzheimers disease, offering hope for patients and their families.',
                    'New Research Shows Promise for Alzheimers Disease Treatment', 1);

            INSERT INTO "public"."users" ("id", "login", "password", "role")
            VALUES (1, 'Admin', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'ADMIN'),
                   (2, 'username123', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (3, 'fearlessrunner', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (4, 'musiclover27', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (5, 'adventureseeker', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (6, 'techguru99', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (7, 'smarthacker76', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER'),
                   (8, 'coolcat85', '$2a$10$SHt9oDxjugnvbgw2gNsp6.Lz9PjjkL0E7rVVBU.g7P7nBlMWeLQZG', 'SUBSCRIBER');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>